Hello
hello friends welcome to AppTalk friends
Bajaj Finance, the giant company of NVC sector has
declared its quarterly result date and there is
a good news for the shareholders of the company,
so without wasting much time let us find out
when the quarterly result of the company is going to come and
what is the good news for its shareholders, so
friends here is the
official note of Bajaj Finance, on this the company had
filed a change in this notice, you
can first see it here,
a board meeting has been fixed by the board of directors of the company on 26th April, that is,
it is confirmed that the quarterly result of the company will come on 26th April itself, now see the good news
for the shareholders of Bajaj Finance here,
dividend, yes
friends the company is thinking of giving dividend to its shareholders,
but first on
26th April in the board meeting there will be a
discussion on this dividend, that is Talent,
if the vote is approved, after that the
shareholders of Bajaj Finance can enjoy this video  If you
can, then you can say that
we are getting very good news from Bajaj Finance.
Now on 26th we will
see what its quarterly
results are like. So friends, that's all for now. If
you are new to the channel, then
keep subscribing to this channel because
we keep bringing updates related to the share market
on this channel. So, we will meet
in the next video. Till then, goodbye.